I would like to have a discussion on electromagnetic fields now.
In other words electronics in the bedroom.
So our lives are full of electronics, electronics is everywhere.
So and it radiates different frequencies and we are exposed all day long to it.
So our immune system is really getting bitten.
And you want to have this one room in your life where you can come home at night and rest from all of the exposure.
You really don't want to have too much electronics in your bedroom.
You don't want to have all those TV’s and DVDs players and phones and it's very important not to have your alarm clock and phone right by your head so that I see quite often.
So if you can Jane here has simple quartz clock that she changed from an electric clock so this is much safer.
So if you really need to have that electronics in the bedroom just put it as far away from you as possible.
Also what's important to know what's behind that headboard, what's behind on the other side of the wall.
I had a client who had the walls full of electronics on the other side and she had constant headaches and her immune system was really suffering and she didn't know why.
So after I pointed out they actually moved electronics in the other room to the other corner and her health improved dramatically after that.